Now, we don't accept requests for rooms and roommates,
ボドウェルでは、部屋のタイプやルームメイトのリクエストは受けておりません。
and here's why
その理由は
At Bodwell our dormitory rooms are organized into halls
寮の部屋はホール（グループ）で分けられており、
There is a wide variety of room shapes. sizes, and locations.
部屋の形、サイズおよびその配置が異なります
For new students, when they arrive boys and girls are divided
新入生は到着した後、
and then grouped into halls
男女別々に
to mix up their ages and their countries.
さまざまな国籍、年齢のホールに分けられます。
Within these halls,
これらの各ホール内には、
Students are assigned by advisors to rooms
ホールアドバイザーが割り当てられています。
We make sure there are at least 2 languages spoken in each room
各部屋に少なくとも2か国語が話されるように、生徒の部屋割りを行い、それを確認します。
Each day through boarding life
毎日の寮生活を通じて
our students overcome problems
生徒達は問題を解決、克服をしていきます。
they meet new people
また、新しい出会いがあり、
they use English to make diverse friends
英語を通じて、さまざま新しい友達をつくる事もできます。
All of these are important life skills
これらはすべて重要なライフスキルです。
Now, after 10 days of arriving
到着から10日後、
students wishing to change their rooms
もし部屋を変更したい場合、
can ask their advisor
担当のホールアドバイザーにリクエストできます。
Their advisor will consider the request and make a decision
彼らのホールアドバイザーは、受け取った要求や理由を検討し、最終判断を下します。
If somebody wants a room change they would usually come to their advisor
生徒がホールアドバイザーに部屋の変更を申し出る理由として、
and say they have a problem with their roommate
ルームメイトと問題があった場合や、
or they don't like their room
部屋が気に入らない場合などが多いですが、
and we talk about what that is and talk about a solution
私たちは、問題の根本を話し合い、できるだけ解決できるよう手助けをし、
to actually make sure they are comfortable in their room.
寮生活が心地よいものになるようサポートします。
Usually what students realize is they get an opportunity
このようなプロセスを通して、生徒は
to practice conflict resolution and conflict management
建設的な問題解決の方法や、問題管理を学んでいき、
and see what that looks like and how to compromise
状況を理解し、妥協点などを見つけ、
with that they get to know other students from different cultures
異なる文化を持つ学生と理解を深めます。
they get to know other students that speak different languages
異なる言語を話す他の生徒と知り合い、
and they end up ultimately staying in the room they were originally put in
親睦を深め、強い友情関係を築き、
because they end up building strong relationships with the students they're there with
最終的には、部屋を変更しないケースがとても多くあります。
We hope your children will be very happy and comfortable here, living in the dormitory
私たちは、すべての生徒達が、寮で快適に過ごせることを願いつつ、
However we really hope the students make the best of this opportunity
この恵まれた機会に、異なる文化、環境で育ってきた
to learn how to live with different people
他国の生徒との生活を通じて
...very essential for international careers
これからの国際化社会に欠かせないスキルを培い、
and getting ready for university
将来に役立てもらうことを心から望んでいます。